{
    "kind": "Dropdown",
    "questions": [
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct question\n",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M1L1a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "___",
                    "options": [
                        "What your name?",
                        "What's your name?",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Choose that or those.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M3L11a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are ___ ?",
                    "options": [
                        "that",
                        "those",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What's ___ ?",
                    "options": [
                        "that",
                        "those",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What's ___ ?",
                    "options": [
                        "that",
                        "those",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are ___  ?",
                    "options": [
                        "that",
                        "those",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What's ___ ?",
                    "options": [
                        "that",
                        "those",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Choose the correct word.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M3L11b.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "___ is a zebra.",
                    "options": [
                        "This",
                        "That",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "___ are lions.",
                    "options": [
                        "These",
                        "Those",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "___ are zebras.",
                    "options": [
                        "These ",
                        "Those",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "___ is a zebra.",
                    "options": [
                        "This",
                        "That",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "___ a gorilla",
                    "options": [
                        "This",
                        "That",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "___ an elephant.",
                    "options": [
                        "This",
                        "That's",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "title": "Choose and write the correct words.",
            "Nomenclatura": "WBP1M5L25a.json",
            "header": "",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I'm Lisa. These are __ paints.",
                    "options": [
                        "my",
                        "their",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "my",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is Ana. These are __ crayons.",
                    "options": [
                        "his",
                        "her",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "her",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "We love projects. This is a picture of __ house.",
                    "options": [
                        "Their",
                        "Its",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 0,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Their",
                    "type": "text"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Jimmy! __ writing is very good!",
                    "options": [
                        "His",
                        "Your",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": 1,
                    "type": "dropdown"
                },
                {
                    "question": "__",
                    "options": [
                        "",
                        "",
                        "",
                        ""
                    ],
                    "correct": "Your",
                    "type": "text"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}